Morning!
Is that for Elsa?
Yes.
You locked her up last night.
She must be furious.
You love Elsa very much,
why must it come to this?
Because she's getting out of hand.
Just like her sister.
Elsa has always been a good kid.
Looks like she must really love this guy.
They just started dating.
How much in love can she be?
If we force them apart,
what if she'll end up like Emma?
Locking her up will not work.
What else can we do?
We're leaving tomorrow night.
After we settle down over there,
we'll have a long talk with her.
What will happen over there?
What else? We'll start over.
You're doing so well here
and you have a good job.
You're giving up everything for me.
What do you mean? We're family.
I won't be separated from you.
Why don't you stay?
Elsa and I will go back, OK?
You think I'll let that happen?
What if you run into that creep?
That's too dangerous.
I have no appetite. I'm not eating.
I'll head back to work.
Don't get any ideas.
You're awake. Want some breakfast?
Now I know why Emma had to leave.
We have the same fate.
Daddy won't let me out either.
You'll be free in two days.
Free? I can't even have friends.
You asked me all those questions that night,
because you're in love with this guy?
His name is YY.
We became friends because
he helped me look for Emma.
He's smart and is good to me
and is always thinking for me.
Just like when I found something about Emma
and wanted to call the Police.
He stopped me
because he didn't want the Police
to know about me.
If he wanted to hurt me,
why would he do that?
But Daddy won't believe him
and insisted YY was up to no good.
Daddy has his reasons.
Mom, can you let me out?
You met YY at the wrong time.
Wait till we settle down abroad
and you have proper proof of identity,
he can join us there.
Wait? How long must I wait?
I only want to see him one last time.
Now I know loving someone can be so hard.
I don't want to leave and be away from YY.
I'll do my best to protect you.
Are you willing to spend
the rest of your life with me
and build a family?
Just be patient.
If he's your Mr. Right like your Daddy,
you two will always be together.
The number you called
cannot be connected now.
She won't pick up or return my messages.
Please be OK.
Excuse me, have you seen this girl?
Excuse me, have you seen her?
Sorry...have you seen this girl?
No!
Thanks.
Excuse me, have you seen her, Uncle?
Young man, you already asked me
this morning.
Sorry!
I'm finished with lunch,
you're still looking for her?
You love her that much?
I'm worried.
Didn't hear from her all night.
I'm afraid something happened to her.
Don't be silly.
She wants to ditch you.
That's why she's ghosting you.
You expect one month's notice?
There are other trees in the forest.
Find someone else.
Don't torture yourself over one girl.
She's not the type to give up easily.
However hard it is, I want to be with her.
YY, I promised you
we'll meet again before I leave.
But I guess by the time you get this letter,
I should have left. Sorry!
Once I settle down, I'll be in touch.
We'll meet again if it's in our destiny.
What are you doing?
Writing a letter to YY.
Since you won't let me out,
I must find a way to say goodbye.
Mom, promise me you'll make sure
he gets this.
He'll be worried if he didn't hear from me.
Please, Mom?
I'm not sending this to him.
Here...
What do you mean?
You want me to say goodbye on the phone?
I want you to tell him in person
you're leaving.
After you settle down, you will contact him.
Really?
Thanks, Mom!
What made you change your mind?
I was going to the bank...
I saw YY looking everywhere for you.
People told him to give up,
but he said he wants to be with you.
What a fool!
I can tell he loves you very much
and cares a great deal about you.
You were right. He'll take good care of you.
Mom, I knew you'll like him.
I won't separate you by force.
Because you have a good relationship.
You must treasure it.
I will.
OK, go find him.
Remember to be home before dark.
Today is Daddy's last day.
He should leave early.
Alright?
Don't worry! I don't want to leave YY,
I also don't want to leave you and Daddy.
I won't abandon you.
Did something happen? I'm very worried.
I'm looking for you near your house.
The number you called cannot be connected.
Please try again later.
What now? You're not picking up!
Hey, Miss!
Are you talking to me?
You're the girl!
Sorry, I don't know you.
Are you looking for a good looking
young man with fair skin?
Yes!
He went over there looking for you!
Thank you, uncle!
Hurry! Before someone grabs
a good catch like him.
YY!
(Sweet dreams)
(is what he said as he went underground)
Over there!
(away from me into the dark)
(Forced me)
(from all my innocence into the very
ordinary day today)
(Watch and wait and see what comes)
(from the soul of the man who is uncertain)
(When the sand washes out to the sea)
I can finally see you again.
(when the dreams fall away)
I'm so worried...so worried about you.
(will there still be someone
there for me...)
I was afraid you'd leave without
saying goodbye!
(for me)
Don't be silly! Why would I do that?
You're holding me so tight I can't breathe.
(He sings and)
I'm not letting go.
(with his hands he holds a microphone)
Childish!
(and speaks so loud for all to hear)
(I'd give)
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
(whatever is left of all the work I'd do)
The battery died because you kept calling.
(my hands are tired from all the years)
Did the Police arrest Ken?
The creep denied killing Emma!
He won't even admit he was Emma's boyfriend.
No way!
When I looked for him at HKIU,
he admitted it
and conned me into following him
to the studio.
If he denied it, you wouldn't follow him.
Then he couldn't blackmail your father.
You're right.
No wonder in the CCTV footage,
he practically ignored Emma.
Ken also told Kwan Sir
Emma's boyfriend is someone called James.
Who's James?
Ken said James is also from Hong Kong
but emigrated to the UK many years ago.
A year ago, he was at HKIU on an
exchange program
and he met Ken.
Ken took him to the bar where he met Emma.
They started dating.
But three months ago,
the exchange program ended,
and they maintained a
long distance relationship.
Ken said James knew he had the connections
so James asked him to help smuggle
Emma to the UK.
Emma said her dream was to
venture out into this world.
I only know if I don't leave,
I'll regret it in the future.
So her boyfriend is in the UK.
No wonder she wanted to run away.
She was so close to getting
her dream come true.
Kwan Sir said near Meow Lung Kee,
a regular customer at the nearby store,
told him on the night of the 8th,
a man wearing a dark green windbreaker
chased a girl who might be Emma.
Look, James has a similar windbreaker.
You mean James is in Hong Kong?
Very likely.
Kwan Sir already contacted Immigration,
to see if he entered Hong Kong recently.
If he did, he's a prime suspect.
Emma told me she's crazy about
her boyfriend.
If they're in love,
why would James kill Emma?
According to Ken,
Emma wanted to go to the UK.
James wasn't so keen.
What does that mean?
James wrote in here he's in Law School.
If Emma smuggled into the UK
he'll be assisting an illegal alien.
If anyone should find out,
he can't be a lawyer.
But that's no reason to kill someone.
Another possibility is money.
Emma was carrying so much money.
He got greedy and had to silence her.
Emma ran away from home because of him.
How could he do this?
It's just my guess.
I'll send a post asking for anyone
with dash cam footage of Emma
after she left the guesthouse
and see why she didn't get on the boat.
I think...we need to start from scratch.
But I may not be able to go with you.
You're leaving so soon?
Tomorrow night.
How are you leaving?
I don't know. Daddy made the arrangements.
It'll be dangerous.
Why don't we talk to your father
and see if there are other options?
No. He saw you dropping me off yesterday.
He got so angry he locked me in my room.
Luckily, Mom let me out
so I could come see you.
Can you stay?
I wish.
But I promised Mom I'll go home.
I'm worried about your safety.
I'm afraid I won't see you again.
No.
Daddy is very careful,
everything should be all set.
Don't be so worried.
Mom said once we settle down,
you can join us over there.
They won't keep us apart anymore.
What is this?
You left it outside the bar.
An avocado?
So it fell out of the bag
and you found it?
Can you grow avocado like that?
It's my first time.
It says online it's very hard.
But since you dropped it, I'll do my best.
I'll keep trying
until it can germinate and bear fruit.
Kwan Sir tracked James down.
He landed in Hong Kong in the afternoon
on the 9th.
He's still here.
We tracked Emma till the 8th
and we lost track of her.
Her time of death was between
the 8th and the 10th.
James was probably the last person she saw.
Where is James now?
When he filled out his landing card,
he put down Hotel Cozy.
Kwan Sir already sent someone there.
I don't want to wait around.
There's still time, let's check it out.
Mrs. Sit, the baby is fine.
Thanks. Dr. Hong!
Since you past your first trimester,
we can use medication for your vaginitis.
I'll prescribe something
and you must finish the course.
I'm taking three weeks off.
I went over your case with Dr. Lam
who will keep me posted of your situation.
You have nothing to worry about.
Dr. Hong, you're so accountable,
I'm not worried at all.
Sorry! Let me get that.
Hello? Yes.
The uterine polypectomy for Mrs. Ng
was passed to Dr. Ma, yes...
Mrs. Sit! Let's go fill your prescription.
OK!
Dr. Hong, you're busier on leave
than when you're at work.
Give me the file.
Oh dear! Mrs. Sit is allergic to this drug.
I prescribed the wrong drug. Go stop her!
Hurry!
OK!
Elsa, where are you?
What time will you be home?
You're home!
Yes.
Just now I prescribed the wrong
drug for a patient.
Luckily I caught it in time,
or the result would be unthinkable.
You have too much on your mind.
Don't blame yourself.
Where's Elsa? Is she packed?
She...was up all night.
Let her sleep a bit longer.
What's in the box?
Hospital documents and bank letters.
I'll go shred them.
Elsa, where are you? Daddy is home.
Where's Elsa's phone?
Where's Elsa? Is she packed?
She...was up all night.
She's sound asleep right now.
Let her sleep a bit longer.
Felix, since we're leaving,
I guess we won't be coming back.
Can you take a walk with me?
The hospital just called.
Something urgent came up and they want me
to handle it.
I'll do that when I get back, OK?
Did Felix find out I let Elsa out?
I think it's odd.
If James was the killer,
why is he still here?
We'll know when we find him.
I'll go find out.
Excuse me, I'm looking for your guest
Chan Lap-jim.
Sorry, we can't disclose our
guest's privacy.
Why didn't you call back?
I think Daddy realized I let you out.
He went out to look for you.
Oh dear! I missed Mom's message.
Daddy must be looking for me everywhere.
You were meeting your friend in our cafe,
but he didn't show up.
You're worried he passed out in his room?
He has a health condition, I'm worried.
All I can say is you don't have to worry.
He went out?
I see.
Do you know where he went?
He just came to Hong Kong,
he doesn't know his way around.
Well...most people ask us about
scenic spots.
But someone asked me the way to
Wan Sing Industrial Building yesterday.
Thanks. Wan Sing Industrial Building.
Thank you...
Wan Sing Industrial Building...
Your family called?
Yes. She said Daddy knew I went out.
You should hurry home.
I'll keep looking.
No. Whether I go home now or later,
I'll get a scolding from Daddy anyway.
I'd rather go with you to find James.
I want to meet Emma's boyfriend.
Let's hurry.
You think we should tell Kwan Sir
what we found out about James?
We don't know what he's doing there
or if he's even there at all.
Let's wait till we find out more.
Come on.
Well? Did you find Chan Lap-jim?
Nothing.
James checked into Room 701 of Hotel Cozy.
But according to the room card record,
he hasn't been back since last night.
He's on the run? He's hiding something.
Anything on the human trafficking cartel?
What we found out so far checked out.
Ching Sir spoke to the Narcotics Bureau (NB)
they're following up on a
human trafficking cartel
that is also involved in drug trafficking.
They'll let us know once they hear anything.
Good.
I heard the snakehead Brother Man is mean.
I can't believe they're into drugs as well.
If he knew Hong Ka-lam had
that much money,
he's likely to kill her.
Other than Chan Lap-jim,
these guys are likely the last people
to see Hong Ka-lam alive.
We must find them soon.
Hello? Yes...where?
OK, thanks!
They found their hideout.
In Wan Sing Industrial Building.
Once NB gets the search warrant,
we can bust them.
I wonder where James is.
We need to check all these units
one by one?
Why did he come here?
It's Daddy! Over there...
It's really him!
What is he doing here?
How many times have you been to a bar?
When did you set a tracker on my phone?
That's outrageous!
Daddy put in a GPS tracker on Emma's phone.
Maybe he did the same to mine.
Shall I turn off the phone?
Yes, but not now.
This way.
Where are we going?
Somewhere far away.
Will Daddy find us?
Trust me.
Let's go.
There's no signal?!
Maybe reception is poor on her phone.
She can't be too far away.
Your father probably won't expect
us to come back.
You're so brilliant! What now?
Wai, don't you look smart in that jacket!
You think so? It's a bit too big.
Not really.
That looks like the one James has.
Follow him.
Wait up...
Stop! I told you I'm not a cop.
The cops busted my hideout in
Meow Lung Kee.
If you're not a cop, how did you find us?
I don't know about any raids.
I'm looking for my girlfriend Hong Ka-lam.
Why is he looking for Emma here?
It doesn't sound like he killed her.
You're making this up to get away.
I'm not lying.
Ken told me I can find you here.
Ken who? You're making it up...
Call the Police!
Boss, those two are snooping around.
The dude is calling someone.
Who are you?
Wrong floor.
Stop!
Come back!
Go!
Hey...
Help...
Come back here...
No...
Run...
Get him!
No...
Take him inside.
Move!
Boss, we've got them.
What should we do with these two?
What now? Are they cops?
Don't be stupid! Do they look like cops?
But they heard what we said.
Lock them up for now.
Move!
Get down!
You too.
No games!
Are you hurt?
No. And you?
I'm fine.
Who are you?
James, right? We've been looking for you.
You know me?
I'm Emma's sister, Hong Ka-yee, Elsa.
I know you're Emma's boyfriend.
We've been looking for you.
You're Emma's sister?
I know Emma has a sister,
but she never told me your name.
Where is Emma?
She was supposed meet me in the UK.
She contacted me before she boarded the boat
but I don't know if she has
got on it or not.
I was so worried
I came here right away to look for her.
What are you doing here?
Did Ken tell you about this place?
Ken is such a jerk.
I entrusted him with helping Emma
skip town.
Not only did he try to rob her,
he also wounded her.
I've been trying to find him
since I arrived
and he's been dodging me.
Luckily I asked him about the
human trafficking cartel before.
That's why I know this place.
Where is Emma?
Emma is dead.
She was the faceless corpse in the news.
What? Emma is dead?
How? And why?
That's what we want to know.
The Police is looking for the killer.
Who killed her?
We thought it was Ken at first.
But he only admitted to wounding
and robbing her.
He denied killing her.
I don't think it was him.
Emma spoke to me on the phone
before she boarded the boat
and told me she was almost at the pier.
I didn't think Ken caught up with her.
But a witness said
near the hillside where they found Emma
he saw a tall man chasing Emma.
He was wearing a dark green windbreaker.
I saw on Instabook,
you had the exact same windbreaker.
You think I killed Emma?
I love her. Why would I kill her?
Ken said he could sense that
you didn't want Emma to go to the UK.
Is that so?
It's not what you think...
Emma told me before
your father found out you guys
went to a bar
and he was likely to confiscate your phones.
If I couldn't get in touch with her
I need not worry about her.
(Day 1 after Emma left)
I finally get to see you. Are you OK?
Why are you in a taxi?
I ran away from home.
I have made up my mind.
I'm not going back.
Where can you go if you don't go back?
I'll come to you. I want to be with you.
Ken has the connections,
he'll find a way to help us.
You're being impulsive.
You left home without a plan.
I've been locked up for three weeks.
I planned everything.
Just tell Ken to contact people
who can send me to you.
I also took money from Daddy's safe.
We can finally be together.
Don't you want that?
OK...I'll get Ken to help you.
Bye!
(Day 3 after Emma left)
Why are you bleeding?
Ken tried to rob me!
Luckily I got most of it back.
Since it was getting late,
I told her to hurry over to Meow Lung Kee.
Because she can't miss the boat.
(Ngan Kai Bay Pier)
Meow Lung Kee is the code name
for Ngan Kai Bay Pier.
Follow this path for ten minutes,
you'll see a steep road
and the pier is right there.
It's so complicated.
It's dark and I'm scared.
Just keep going.
Judging from your current location,
you're not far from the pier.
Once you get on the boat, I'll see you soon.
You're breaking up, reception is poor.
Call me after you land.
I'll come get you right away.
OK, bye!
I lost track of her after that.
I was worried and I thought...
maybe there was no signal on the boat.
But not long after that,
she sent me a message
telling me she'd rather stay in Hong Kong.
I thought that was odd.
Why did she change her mind so suddenly?
No matter how many messages I sent her,
she never texted back.
I became very worried
and caught the next flight to Hong Kong.
After I landed, I still couldn't
get in touch with her.
Emma was very protective of her family.
She never told me where she lived.
Then I thought the snakehead should know
what happened to Emma on the boat
on that night.
I asked Ken about the
human trafficking cartel.
But he only told me the name of
an industrial building.
But I didn't get the name right.
I only remember Wan something
Industrial Building.
It took me a long time to find
my way here.
When I finally came here...
Who are you?
I asked them if they have seen
Emma on the 8th.
They pulled me inside
and asked me how I found them.
I told them Ken told me.
We heard you from outside.
But they didn't seem to know Ken.
Maybe Ken went through someone else.
I didn't find out anything
and got beaten up.
Trust me. I only wanted to find Emma.
I didn't kill her.
I believe you.
If you killed her,
you should have left town.
Why would you be here?
Why didn't I come back sooner?
Why did I let her board the boat by herself?
I thought Ken was right about you
and you didn't want Emma to find you
in the UK.
If Emma smuggled into the UK,
you probably can't be a lawyer.
Yes, I hesitated.
I thought I could wait till I finish school
and come back to Hong Kong to be with her.
But I knew at that moment,
Emma didn't want to stay at home anymore.
She had no one else but me.
I made up my mind
I'll give up being a lawyer.
I already applied with the university
to change my major.
After she arrived in the UK,
we'll keep a low profile
and live a simple life.
But now, it won't happen...
Emma should be very touched
to hear you say this.
I'm sure she heard me.
Let's try to get out of here.
What are you doing?
Sit down!
You overheard everything.
I'll give each of you a shot
and then throw you in the water.
Do it!
Yes, Boss!
You first!
No...
Don't move!
You...
You hit me?
Boss, cops are outside!
Clear out!
Run...
Police! Freeze!
Police! Nobody moves! Raise your hands!
Police! Stay where you are!
Police! Freeze!
Get down!
Don't resist!
Run...
Don't move...
Get down...
You should go. I'll call you.
I'm leaving tomorrow night.
I'll call you tonight.
Kwan Sir!
YY...what are you doing here?
Long story. I'll go with you
and give you a statement.
Let's go...
You're late!
Where's Daddy?
Felix, tonight is our last night
in this house.
Let's just enjoy our last dinner, OK?
OK, let's eat.
OK?
I made a mistake today.
I prescribed the wrong drug to a patient.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Don't blame yourself.
But...I'm a doctor.
I cannot make mistakes.
Because some mistakes are irreversible.
Elsa...
your sister ran away from home
and it was my mistake.
I already lost your sister,
I can't lose you too.
That's why I'm so hard on you,
Do you understand?
I do.
After we leave here, we can start over.
Hello, YY?
Elsa, is everything OK at home?
They didn't scold me.
It was actually my fault.
I snuck out and made Daddy worried.
That's why he followed me.
Did you give your statement?
Kwan Sir asked me who you are.
I told him I don't know you.
I don't think he believed me.
But he can't do anything to me.
Good. I was worried about
getting you involved.
I'm calling you about something
very important.
Promise me you'll stay calm.
Shall we take this with us?
Sure!
Phone?
Yes, I'm going tonight.
Why do you have two phones?
This is my new chat app.
I'll contact you on my new phone.
Remember this icon.
Daddy is hiding Emma's phone.
I'm calling you about something
very important.
Promise me you'll stay calm.
What is it? You sound serious.
Remember I told you this morning,
I'll send a post to ask for
any dash cam footage of Emma
after she left the guesthouse.
I remember.
I just received a clip,
between 4 and 5 o'clock
near the guesthouse.
I'm sending it to you now.
(Share with Elsa?)
OK!
He was chasing your sister.
Grabbed her and tried to take her somewhere.
but your sister got away.
That was Daddy.
He saw her on the 8th.
Why did he lie?
He said he went out every day
but didn't find Emma.
Wait...look at the jacket he was wearing.
It looks so much like James'.
The customer of the store said
he saw a man chasing a girl,
wearing a dark green windbreaker
and was 175cm tall.
Is that your father's height?
You suspect he killed Emma?
No, it's impossible.
Daddy loves us very much.
Even if Emma disobeyed him,
he couldn't have killed her.
Elsa, calm down.
I'm not saying he's the killer.
It's a possibility.
Why else did he lie about seeing Emma?
No, it can't be.
If your father was the killer,
the new phone Emma was using
when she left
should be in his possession.
Try to look for it.
Did Daddy really kill Emma?
Hello, YY! I found Emma's new phone.
That means on the 8th,
your father found Emma near
the guesthouse
and he followed her
all the way to Meow Lung Kee.
Emma refused to come home with him.
He got so angry...he killed Emma.
Then he took her phone,
posed as Emma and sent a message to James
to break up with him
so James won't suspect
why Emma didn't get on the boat.
When I suspected the corpse was Emma.
He posed as Emma again
and sent me a message to tell me
she was safe.
Just so I will stop looking into it.
Elsa, you're in grave danger.
Don't stay in the house.
Drop everything...
find an excuse and leave.
But...
Elsa? Hello?
Hello? Elsa...
Elsa?